# Bardhi Grainca

Bardhi.grainca@hotmail.com - (389) 76-466-033 - Skopje, Macedonia - My Website

I'm a designer who codes. I am currently doing my MSc in Software Eng. In my free time I'm always searching for new challenges to conquer, because design and coding is my passion. I am a bit of a Jack – or Jill – of all design trades. Being well-versed allows me to maintain full aesthetic control when building brands – touching on everything from Information Architecture, UI/UX and mobile apps, to illustrating icons, graphics and logos. I also have 2 years of working experience in DevOps Infrastructures and my strong culture for enterprise DevOps teams has been engraved in my daily life and is part of me.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Singular Nov 2019 – April 2019

## **DevOps Engineer**

Skopje

- Continuous integration (CI) continuous delivery (CD) with Jenkins
- Monitoring with Grafana (Percona), PRTG
- Troubleshooting application bugs
- Database management (MySQL)
- Log management (Graylog)
- Python Scripts, Bash Scripts

## Stopanska Banka Main Branch

Jan 2019 - Nov 2019

System analyst

Skopie

- Collaborating with Business Analysts, Project Leads to resolve issues and ensuring solutions are viable
- Creating system guidelines and manuals for the organization
- Troubleshooting technical issues

SEAVUS Nov 2017 – Jan 2019

## It and Operation Engineer

Skopje

- Diagnosing and solving customer software problems
- Provide technical assistance to the costumers like VOLVO, Rolls Royce, Ford, Tesla, and NATO.
- Test and reproduce reported issues and answer the technical questions, resolve customer problems.
- Provide assistance concerning the use of computer hardware and software, including operating systems and application, databases, network, security.

## Web Design, Graphic design

Nov 2015 - Present

#### Freelancer

Skopje

- As a part-time freelancer I've worked on smaller and bigger projects.
- I have worked with Allran Electric, RealRok, Fahrenheit Mechanical NYC, SBNY Construction Company, on their corporate identity and web design/development.

## **EDUCATION**

#### South East European University

2014 - 2017

Degree (BS), Majors (Computer Science)

Skopje

- Won 2 certificates on leadership and coding, also been part of NASA Space App Challenge
- I've won 1 place 2 years in a row in swimming competition

#### **SKILLS & INTERESTS**

- Skills: MySQL, SOAP, TOAD, LDAP, APACHE, .NET, SAP, Customer Service 1nd Level, 2nd Level;
- System Administrator, Windows Server 14, 16, Linux, VMware;
- Prototyping in XD, PSD, Al and converting them into Functional Web pages.
- HTML/CSS/Java Script, jQuery, UX/UI, Bootstrap, Python, Bash Scripting

Interests: Puns; Sleeping; Web-Design; Politics; Traveling;